The term Virtual Private Cloud,
术语虚拟私有云
or VPC for short, sounds pretty intimidating.
或者简称 VPC 听起来挺吓人的
Really, every part of the acronym is a little intense.
真的 首字母缩写词的每一部分都有点紧张
Virtual, private, and cloud all have a lot of connotations.
虚拟 私有和云都有很多内涵
So what is a VPC?
什么是 VPC?
If you've configured a traditional network infrastructure,
如果您配置了传统的网络基础架构
you'll find VPCs fairly familiar.
你会发现 VPC 相当熟悉
A VPC is primarily a network.
VPC 主要是一个网络
It's virtual because any resource you create in AWS is virtual.
它是虚拟的 因为在 AWS 中创建的任何资源都是虚拟的
It's private because it's yours.
这是私人的因为这是你的
Just like a physical network that you own,
就像你拥有的物理网络
you control what goes in and out of the network,
你控制了网络的发生和发生
and you decide where to put your service within the network.
并决定将您的服务置于网络中的位置
The cloud part is really redundant to virtual,
云部分真的是多余的虚拟的
and it just makes it sound extra special.
这让它变得格外特别
VPCs are isolated private networks that are
VPC 是孤立的专用网络
customizable to your needs and are region-specific.
可定制为您的需求 并且是特定于区域的
There are some aspects of VPCs that are
VPC 的某些方面是
more AWS constructs than they are strictly networking.
与严格联网相比  AWS 构造更多
Security groups, for example,
例如 安全组
are similar to firewalls but not exactly the same.
与防火墙相似 但不完全相同
The way that traffic gets into and out of
交通进入和离开的方式
a VPC is a little different, similar but different.
一个 VPC 有点不同 类似但不一样
AWS provides constructs to allow traffic from the Internet directly to your service,
AWS 提供构造以允许流量直接从因特网到您的服务
or you can have traffic flow outbound through network address translation devices.
或者您可以通过网络地址转换设备进行流量出站
We'll look more at this later.
我们回头再看看
You can connect VPCs together.
您可以将 VPC 连接在一起
You can peer two VPCs in your account even if they're in different regions.
您可以在帐户中对等两个 VPC  即使它们位于不同的区域
You can connect two VPCs from different AWS accounts,
您可以从不同的 AWS 帐户连接两个 VPC
although, obviously, you should be cautious about doing this.
虽然很明显你应该谨慎从事这件事
How many VPCs you use is up to you.
您使用的 VPC 有多少
Depending on what network components you use,
根据您使用的网络组件
a VPC can have almost no cost.
一个 VPC 几乎没有成本
Given this, you have a lot of freedom to decide what makes sense for you.
鉴于这一点 你有很多自由决定什么是对你有意义的
If you're running your application in one region,
如果你在一个地区运行应用程序
you can run a fully multi AZ mode with just one VPC.
您可以仅使用一个 VPC运行完全多 AZ 方式
Having one VPC per region is actually the default setup within AWS.
每个区域有一个 VPC 实际上是 AWS 中的缺省设置
AWS now creates a default VPC for you in every region.
AWS 现在在每个区域为您创建缺省 VPC
However, you can delete this if you desire.
但是 如果您愿意 可以将其删除
You can have multiple VPCs per region.
每个区域可以有多个 VPC
You can treat multiple VPCs as entirely standalone networks,
您可以将多个 VPC 视为完全独立的网络
or you can connect them together to form a larger network hierarchy.
或者可以将它们连接在一起以形成更大的网络层次结构
Really, you can combine VPCs in just about any way that you would like.
实际上 您可以将 VPC 与您所希望的任何方式结合起来
You can also connect your office or data center directly to
您还可以直接将办公室或数据中心连接到
your VPC and thus extend your office network into AWS.
您的 VPC  从而将您的办公网络扩展到 AWS
So what things are in a VPC?
那么  VPC中有哪些东西 ?
Anything that is instance-based will run inside of VPC.
基于实例的任何内容都将在 VPC内部运行
For example, RDS, ElastiCache, DocumentDB,
例如  RDS  ElastiCache  DocumentDB
Elasticsearch, EMR, EC2, Load Balancers,
Elasticsearch  EMR  EC2 负载均衡器
Neptune, Redshift, lots of things.
Neptune   Redshift 很多东西
What are the things that do not run inside of a VPC?
未在 VPC 内部运行的内容是什么 ?
The more service-oriented AWS services tend to not run in a VPC.
更面向服务的 AWS 服务通常不会在 VPC中运行
Any of the global services as well as several core services,
任何全球服务以及若干核心服务
such as SNS or SQS are actually services that are accessed directly over the Internet.
例如 SNS 或 SQS 实际上是直接通过因特网访问的服务
Some of these include S3, DynamoDB, CloudFront, SNS,
其中一些包括 S3  DynamoDB  CloudFront  SNS
SQS, SES, Route 53,
SQS   SES  Route 53
API Gateway, IAM, and Cloud Trail.
API Gateway  IAM和 Cloud Trail